(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-23T23:07:20.173679",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
みんなー！
Everyone!
みんなおりゅ〜？
Is everyone here?
なのなのら！
Nano-nanora!
お菓子の国のお姫様
The princess of the Candy Kingdom,
とびきりプリティな0歳児
a super pretty 0-year-old!
ピアノだって弾けるんだし
I can even play the piano,
赤ちゃんじゃないのらよ！
so I'm not a baby, nanorayo!
ワガママだって言うけれど
You call me selfish, but...
ルーナはお姫様なのらから
Luna is a princess, nanorakara!
ルーナイト達も執事も
LuKnights and even the butler...
いちいちうるさいのら！
...are being so noisy about everything, nora!
さぁ ルーナイト達！ 準備はできたのら？
Now then, LuKnights! Are you ready, nora?
出陣なのらー！
To battle, nanora!
パフェもシュワシュワも 早く用意するのら！
Prepare the parfait and carbonated drinks quickly, nora!
あれもこれも食べたいのら！
I want to eat this and that, nora!
おいしいのはひとりじめ
Keeping all the delicious stuff for myself,
まずいのや苦いのは ルーナイト達に差し入れ！
and giving the bad and bitter stuff to the LuKnights!
チョコレートの噴水も
Chocolate fountains,
キャンディの首飾りも
and candy necklaces...
素敵なのたくさんあるのら
There are so many wonderful things, nora!
だからルーナのために集めて来てね♡
So please gather them for Luna, okay? ♡
絶対絶対絶対絶対約束！
Absolute, absolute, absolute, absolute promise!
なのなのら！
Nano-nanora!
まわるまわるまわるまわるーな
Spinning, spinning, spinning, Mawa-Luna!
まわるまわるまわるまわるーなーな
Spinning, spinning, spinning, Mawa-Luna-na!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回ってもっとぐるぐる回って
Spin round and round, spin even more round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回ってみんなぐるぐる回って
Spin round and round, everyone spin round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐるそうやってもっとぐるぐる回って
Spin round and round like that, spin even more round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる笑ってずっとぐるぐるまわルーナ
Smile round and round, forever round and round, Mawa-Luna!
ぐるぐる地球は回り始め幾億年
The Earth has been spinning round and round for hundreds of millions of years...
いつまでもこのまま
Forever just like this...
回るみんなに幸せを...
Happiness to everyone spinning...
まわり続くまわルーナ
Continuing to spin, Mawa-Luna!
ますますます社会がぐるぐるま〜...あれ？
Society goes round and round more and more... Huh?
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回ってもっとぐるぐる回って
Spin round and round, spin even more round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回ってみんなぐるぐる回って
Spin round and round, everyone spin round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる笑ってもっとぐるぐる笑って
Smile round and round, smile even more round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる踊ってみんなぐるぐる踊って
Dance round and round, everyone dance round and round!
ぐるぐるぐるぐる回ってもっと
Spin round and round, even more...
んなぁ～
Nnaa~
ぐるぐるまわるまわるーな
Spinning round and round Luna
まんなかちてん...
Center point...
いつもおとぎ話のお姫様 (はい)
Always a princess in a fairytale (Yes!)
みんなの輝くお月様 (はい)
Everyone's shining moon (Yes!)
今日はおやすみして
Taking a rest today
重い王冠今はおいといて
Putting off the heavy crown for now
どっちの私もしゅきになってくれますか
Will you love both versions of me?
どっちもほしいからまん中にいたくなる
Because I want both, I want to stay in the middle
スニーカーとシャツに着替えて
Changing into sneakers and a shirt
あるき出したんだ
I started walking
出発のアラームは
The departure alarm...
新しい私鳴らしてあげる
I'll sound it, my new self!
両腕をいっぱいにしても
Even if I fill both my arms
ぎゅっとしたいこの気持ち入らない
This squeeze-tight feeling won't fit
片方なんて選べない
I can't choose just one side
迷ってるならまん中なんだよ
If you're lost, the answer is right in the middle!
まんかいの青春
Full-bloom youth
満腹に摂取
Consuming to full satisfaction
まんてん流星群
Full marks meteor shower
満月 in heaven
Full moon in heaven
まんめん笑顔にして
Put on a full-faced smile
満点すぎる思い出
Full-score memories
まんまるーな Happy day!!
Manmaru Luna Happy day!!
せかいのまんなかでプリンセスを忘れるくらい
Right in the middle of the world, enough to forget being a princess
胸まんたんにきゅんっとしてみたい
I want to fill my chest full with that fluttering feeling
どっちだってホントの私
Whichever side, it's the real me
瞬きしたら君のどまんなか
If you blink, I'll be right in the center of your heart
まん中にかさなるちてん
The point where it overlaps in the middle
まん中心でよくばるちてん
The point of being greedy in the middle
まん中のまんなかちてん
The center of the center point
恋する女の子のいいとこ取りで
Taking the best of both worlds as a girl in love
照れ隠しと素直の今まんなかちてん
Between shy pretense and honesty, right now is the middle point
跪きなさい。
Kneel before me.
汝、この城の扉を叩いた者よ。
You who knocked on the gates of this castle.
誓いなさい。
Swear your oath.
このルーナの盾となり矛となり—
To become Luna's shield and spear—
夜はぐっすり眠れるまで
Until you can sleep soundly at night
ともにあることをー！
To always be with me!
捧げなさい！姫でおあるぞ！
Offer yourself! For I am your Princess!
止まるのら！
Stop right there-nora!
紅茶のカップ がちゃがちゃ鳴らさないって えらい！
Not clattering your teacup—how commendable!
スコーンだって こぼさず綺麗に食べて すごい！
Eating your scones neatly without spilling a crumb—amazing!
たまに王冠 どっちが前か間違っちゃうの かわいい！
Occasionally wearing your crown backwards—how cute!
通ってよし！なのら！
You may pass, nano-ra!
開城〜！
Open the gates~!
第一条！ 誰よりルーナが好きな人！
Clause 1! Anyone who loves Luna more than anyone else!
第二条！ シルクのお布団持ってきて！
Clause 2! Bring me a silk blanket!
第三条！ 三時のお茶会来れる人！
Clause 3! Anyone who can attend the 3 o'clock tea party!
守れなかったら 即・制・裁！
If you fail to observe these, immediate sanction!
分かってほしいのら…
I want you to understand-nora...
これも、帝王学を学ぶため……
This too is to study the art of emperorship...
愛という名の…… 教育なのら〜！
It's education... in the name of love-nora~!
守護ってルーナイト 想ってくんないと プロムナードボイコットなのなののら！
Protect me, LuKnight! If you don't care for me, I'll boycott our promenade, nano-nano-nora!
手の甲に 忠誠誓うの Chu!
Swear your loyalty with a kiss on the back of my hand, Chu!
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Slip on the glass slipper and dance a waltz!
守護ってルーナイト かまってくんないと
Protect me, LuKnight! If you don't give me attention
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
No matter how many brownies or candies I have
君がいなきゃだって！
It's no good without you!
みんな 心して
Everyone, prepare your hearts...
捧げなさい！ 姫でおあるぞ！
Offer yourself! For I am your Princess!
守護ってルーナイト 想ってくんないと プロムナードボイコットなのなののら！
Protect me, LuKnight! If you don't care for me, I'll boycott our promenade, nano-nano-nora!
永遠の 忠誠この指に Chu!
Seal your eternal loyalty on this finger, Chu!
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Slip on the glass slipper and dance a waltz!
守護ってルーナイト かまってくんないと
Protect me, LuKnight! If you don't give me attention
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
No matter how many brownies or candies I have
君がいなきゃだって！
It's no good without you!
みんな 心して
Everyone, prepare your hearts...
捧げなさい！ 姫でおあるぞ！
Offer yourself! For I am your Princess!
んなぁ～！みんなぁ、およぉ～！
Nnaa~! Everyone, oyoo~!
ホロライブ4期生 姫森ルーナなのら～！
I'm Hololive 4th Gen's Himemori Luna-nora~!
今日は、ルーナたんの 生誕祭ライブー！
Today is Luna-tan's Birthday Live~!
イエーイ！みんな来てくれてありがとう～！
Yay! Thank you everyone for coming~!
今日のハッシュタグはこちら！
Today's hashtag is this!
＃姫森ルーナ生誕LIVE2025！これでいっぱいツイートしてください！
#HimemoriLunaBirthdayLIVE2025! Please tweet a lot with this!
そして、みんな、ルーナたんの...
And everyone, Luna-tan's...
1曲目だね！どうだったー？
That was my original song! How was it?
可愛かったー？
Was it cute?
ふむふむ、ふむふむ、可愛い可愛い、分かってたのらー！
Hmm, hmm... "Cute, cute"... I knew it!
そして、今日の会場を見てください！
And look at today's venue!
ででででででで...
Ta-da-da-da-da...
すげー！雲だらけ！
Awesome! It's full of clouds!
あっちのさん...
Look over there...
この雲の向こう何があるのかな？みんな探してみてー！
I wonder what's beyond these clouds? Everyone, try looking for it!
そして、今日のライブテーマはー？ルナ・リバースデイ！
And today's live stream theme is... "Luna Rebirth Day"!
どんな意味があるのか... はてさて
What kind of meaning does it have...? Let's see!
そして、守って、ルーナイト！
And save me, LuKnights!
歌ってる時にルーナイト... 大変身しました！
While I was singing, LuKnight... underwent a huge transformation!
みんな、気づいてくれたのらー？
Did everyone notice?
100万人記念で、新モデルになりましたー！
To celebrate 1 million subscribers, I got a new model!
そして、ホルーナイトが... なんかルーナイトに魔法をかけてくれたのらーね！
And then Holo Knight... cast a spell on me!
ルーナイトー！おーい！
LuKnight! Hey~!
姫！姫！これ！
Princess! Princess! Look!
姫ー！どこにいるのらー？
Princess! Where are you?
わー！この雲の向こうにいます！
Whoa! I'm beyond these clouds!
あー！そうなのらね！
Ah! Is that so?
ねぇねぇ、新しい姿、どう？どう？どう？
Hey, hey, how's my new look? How is it, how is it, how is it?
えっ、めっちゃ可愛いよ！
Eh, it's super cute!
え、本当ー？
Eh, really?
せっかくだから、姫の以前の姿を出して比較してみよう！
Since we're here, let me display Princess's previous model and compare!
あ、いいねいいねいいね！
Ah, sounds good, sounds good, sounds good!
ど、ど、ど、あ、光って出た！出た！パネルが出そう！
D-d-d... Ah, it's glowing! It appeared! It appeared! A panel is coming out!
出た出た出たー！
It came out, came out, came out!
え、見て、どう？
Eh, look, how is it?
ではまずは足元から見ていきましょう！
Then first, let's look from the feet up!
あ、そうそうそう！赤裸々さん、いい感じですよー！
Ah, right right right! Camera person, looking good!
なんかこれ影の感じとか変わった？変わった変わった！
Did something like the shadow effect change? It changed, it changed!
スカートとかコースターの感じ変わったね！可愛いねー！
The skirt and coaster feel changed! Pretty cute!
いい感じ！いい感じ！
Looking good, looking good!
あ、待って、ここら辺とか... 加圧トレーニングの効果が出てるんじゃない？
Ah, wait, around here... Isn't the pressure training paying off?
えっ、出てる？ルーナイト、出てる？
Eh? Is it showing? LuKnight, is it showing?
最近、加圧トレーニングしてる？
Have you been doing pressure training lately?
やってるよ！パーソナルだけどな！
I am! Through personal training, though!
あ、そうそうそう！後ろ見て後ろ！後ろ！
Ah, right right right! Look at the back! The back!
え、後ろ？後ろ？よっ！
Eh, back? Back? Yo!
おー！これこれ！見てこれ！髪の毛の揺れ！あとシルエット感！これめっちゃいいじゃん！
Oh! This, this! Look at this! The hair physics! And the silhouette! Isn't this awesome?
そうそうそう！
Right, right, right!
あと、そしてルーナイトの手も見てほしいのらー！
And also, I want you to look at LuKnight's hands!
わー！お手手が小さくて可愛いねー！
Whoa! The hands are so small and cute!
手相がいい感じ！
The palm lines look nice!
手相？あ、手相ね！
Palm lines? Ah, palm lines!
あと顔見て！
And look at my face!
あー！お顔、このパネルと比べるのはちょっと難しいんだけど、斜めから見た時の、あ！フェイスラインとか変わったね！超可愛いじゃん！
Ah! Comparing the face to this panel is a bit tough, but looking from an angle... Ah! The face line changed! Super cute!
パパ、ありがとー！
Papa, thank you~!
ま、ぜひみんなもね、過去の3D配信と見比べてほしいのらー！
Well, I hope everyone compares it with past 3D streams!
ねぇねぇ、ホリ... ホルーナイト？質問があるんだけど...
Hey hey, Holo... Holo Knight? I have a question...
そっちの雲の向こうってどうなってるのらー？
What's it like beyond those clouds over there?
舞踏会の会場があるよ！来る？
There's a ball venue! Want to come?
えっ、マジ？行くのらー！
Eh, really? I'm going!
馬車ー！
Carriage~!
え、ば、馬車ー？うわー！めっちゃ光ってるー！
Eh, c-carriage? Whoa! It's glowing so much!
うわわわわ！でかーい！これムーンギャラクシーの時ステージに合体してた馬車なのらー！
Whoa whoa whoa! It's huge! This is the carriage that was attached to the stage during Moon Galaxy!
というわけで姫、乗っちゃってください！
So, Princess, please get on!
乗るのらー！
I'm getting on!
うわー！すごい！中も豪華なのらー！
Whoa! Amazing! The inside is so luxurious too!
ちょっとここ座ってみるのらー！よいしょ！
Let me try sitting here! Heave-ho!
ルーナイトの人形もあるのらねー！すごい！
There's even a LuKnight plushie! Awesome!
姫、準備はOKですかー？
Princess, are you ready?
もちろんだ！出発進行なのらー！
Of course! Full steam ahead!
よし、飛びますよー！
Alright, we're taking off!
行こうー！
Let's go~!
動いたー！うわー！進むのらー！
It moved! Whoa~! We're moving forward!
すげー！この馬車、飛んでるのらー！
Awesome! This carriage is flying!
よし、よいしょ！こっち見ってみよう！
Alright, heave-ho! Let me look over here!
うわー！すごーい！
Whoa~! Incredible!
星と雲がめちゃくちゃ綺麗なのおらー！
The stars and clouds are super beautiful!
うわー、眺め最高なのらねー！
Whoa, the view is the best!
ガタガタ動いてますわ！
It's rattling and moving!
いいのらー！こっちからも見てみるのらね！
Nice! Let's take a look from here too!
よいしょ、よいしょ...
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
こっちもすごい！眺め最高ー！
This side is amazing too! The view is the best!
うわー、いい感じなのらー！
Whoa, it feels so nice!
高いなー、でもここ！
Though it's really high up here!
だけどホルーナイトさん、このまま進んだら目の前の立派な雲とぶつかるのらけどさ...
By the way, Holo Knight-san, if we keep going like this, we're gonna crash into those big clouds in front of us...
大丈夫なのら？進んで... 向こうが何も見えないのらよ！
Is it really okay to keep going? I can't see a thing beyond them!
いや
Yeah,
ご安心ください
please rest assured.
このポルーナイトにお任せあれ
Leave it to this Pol-knight!
少々揺れますぞ！
It's going to shake a little!
しっかり掴まっててください！
Please hold on tight!
大丈夫？ 本当に…
Are you sure? Really...
行きますぞー！
Here we go!
本当に大丈夫ー？
Are you really sure?
やばいんじゃないのかな？
Isn't this bad?
雲来てるよー！
The clouds are coming!
うわー！ もう隠れるー！
Whoa! It's totally covering us!
うわー！
Whoa!
Luna RebirthDay 姫森ルーナ 生誕LIVE2025
Luna RebirthDay - Himemori Luna Birthday Live 2025
あたし今 最上級にかわいいの
Right now, I'm at my ultimate level of cute!
君に振られて 最上級にかわいいの
Getting dumped by you makes me ultimate level cute!
これがお乙女の逆襲だ！
This is a maiden's counterattack!
もう気づいてるかもしれないけど言うね
You might have noticed already, but I'll say it anyway.
あたしね 今とても かわいい
You know, right now I'm super cute.
君が始めた恋 君が終わらすなんて
You started this love, and now you're ending it?
なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ かわいい
What's up with that? I'm gonna cry! Still cute!
あたしの連絡だけ 通知OFFにしてたなんて
Muting notifications only for my messages...
友達から聞いたよ
I heard about it from a friend!
「連絡しすぎ」だって 君が不安にさせるからジャン
Saying I message too much? That's because you make me anxious!
もう気にしてないけど だって今
Not that I care anymore, because right now...
君に振られて 最上級にかわいいの
Getting dumped by you makes me ultimate level cute!
自分史上一番ときめき放つわ
Emitting the most heart-throbs in my entire history!
最上級にかわいいの
Ultimate level cute!
認めなよ これがお乙女の逆襲だ！
Admit it! This is a maiden's counterattack!
さすがに失恋直後は
Right after a heartbreak, naturally...
涙でぐちゃぐちゃで かわいい
I was a messy tearful wreck, but still cute!
君が泣かせたのに 雑なサヨナラだった
You made me cry, and yet your goodbye was so careless.
なんだそれ 泣いちゃうぞ かわいい
What's up with that? I'm gonna cry! Still cute!
「二人しか知らない」って 言ってた話だって
Even the story you said "only the two of us know"...
どうしてあの子も知ってるの？
Why does that girl know it too?
別れてよかったなんて 思わせないでほしかった
I wished you hadn't made me think, "I'm glad we broke up."
好きだったから
Because I really loved you...
君に振られて 最上級にかわいくなりました
Getting dumped by you made me ultimate level cute!
むしろありがと 最上級にかわいくなったって
If anything, thanks! Knowing I became ultimate level cute...
ねぇ言って 知って あいつがなんかかわいくなったって ねぇ聞いて
Hey, say it! Know it! Tell everyone she got somehow cuter! Hey, listen!
君に振られて 最上級にかわいいの
Getting dumped by you makes me ultimate level cute!
自分史上一番ときめき放つわ
Emitting the most heart-throbs in my entire history!
最上級にかわいいの
Ultimate level cute!
認めなよ これがお乙女の逆襲だ！
Admit it! This is a maiden's counterattack!
最上級にかわいいの
Ultimate level cute!
君に振られて 最上級にかわいいの
Getting dumped by you makes me ultimate level cute!
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a devoted Cinderella!
退屈な月曜日 あなたの香りで目覚めるの
On a boring Monday, I wake up to your scent.
纏ったトップノート そうよ秘密の物語なの
Wrapped in top notes, yes, it's a secret story.
うまくリプライできない 震えるハート
I can't reply properly, my heart is trembling.
ためらい×はじらい ＝ 空回り…
Hesitation x bashfulness = going in circles...
誘うファンタジー 重なっちゃうくらい一途だもん
An inviting fantasy, because I'm devoted enough to overlap!
あなたに夢中です♡
I'm crazy about you!
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやぁだ！
Ah, I don't want you going viral, going viral!
ねぇ かまってかまってもっと！
Hey, pay attention, pay attention to me more!
誰しもがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone is going after you.
ウインクひとつでメロメロにさせちゃって
Making everyone fall head over heels with a single wink,
こっちの気も知らないで！
without even knowing how I feel!
もー！ バズっちゃバズっちゃやぁだ！
Geez! I don't want you going viral, going viral!
ねぇ 射抜いて射抜いてずっと！
Hey, pierce my heart, pierce my heart forever!
いつでもあなたに翻弄ちゅう
Always being toyed with by you,
誰よりあなたのトクベツでいたいのお
I want to be your special one more than anyone else!
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a single-minded Cinderella!
どんな道が待ってても
No matter what path lies ahead,
ガラスのヒールで駆けてくよ
I'll run in my glass heels.
魔法が解けても覚めない夢を
A dream from which I won't awaken even if the spell wears off...
あなたにあげる
...I'll give it to you.
だからぜったい負けない！
So I definitely won't give up!
脈打つビート
My throbbing beat,
純愛してたい！
I want to love purely!
まっすぐに
Straightforwardly,
想うエンパシー 伝わっちゃうくらい
So much empathy in my feelings, enough to convey
本気だもん
How serious I am.
まさしく無敵です
Truly, I am invincible!
Ah ハマってハマっていいよ
Ah, it's fine to get hooked, totally hooked!
ねえ ディグってディグってきゅんと！
Hey, dig deeper and deeper into your heart!
恋する乙女は変幻自在
A girl in love is ever-changing.
「キレイ」も「キューティー」もよくばりに励めば
If I greedily strive for both "pretty" and "cute,"
輝く自分になるの
I'll become a glowing version of myself!
さぁ！ハマってハマっていいよ
Come on, it's fine to fall for me!
ねえ 気づいて気づいてちゃんと！
Hey, notice me, notice me properly!
まだまだ乙女は日進月歩
A maiden keeps making rapid progress every day!
世界で一番のドキドキがほしいの
I want the greatest excitement in the world!
あなたいけないプリンスです
You are such a naughty prince.
I Love You!
I Need You!
Ah 「好き」って「好き」ってなんで そう「ズキ」って「ズキ」っていうの？
Ah, why does saying "I like you" make my heart throb like that?
けなげなココロは困惑中
My devoted heart is so confused.
愛しさふくらんで こんなにも苦しいの
My affection swells, making it so painful...
いますぐこっちに微笑んで！
Smile at me right now!
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやぁだ！
Ah, I don't want you going viral, no way!
ねえ かまってかまってもっと！
Hey, pay attention to me, pay attention to me more!
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone's targeting you!
ウインクひとつでメロメロにさせちゃって
Making everyone head over heels with a single wink,
こっちの気も知らないで！
Without even knowing how I feel!
もー！バズっちゃバズっちゃやぁだ！
Geez! I don't want you going viral, no way!
ねえ 射抜いて射抜いてずっと！
Hey, pierce my heart forever and ever!
いつでもあなたに翻弄ちゅう
I'm always completely toyed with by you!
誰よりあなたのトクベツでいたいの
I want to be more special to you than anyone else.
あぁ なんてぜいたくな... 許してね
Ah, is that too selfish of me...? Please forgive me.
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a single-minded Cinderella!
オトメロディー
[Song: Otome Lody]
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Love love suu, fluffy fluffy fuu,
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
Feelings like this are a spellbound melody.
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody!
オトナじゃない オトメです
I'm not an adult, I'm a young maiden.
恋するのが仕事です
Falling in love is my job.
君の名前つぶやくと ドキドキするの
Whispering your name makes my heart throb.
聞き分けナイ この胸が
My stubborn heart...
歌い出して止まらない
...starts singing and won't stop!
上手じゃなくて ゴメンナサイ
I'm sorry if I'm not good at it,
だけど聞いて とどけ
But please listen, reach out!
マイメロディー マイメロディー
My Melody, My Melody!
星空を越えて 君の夢 守るリボン
Crossing the starry sky, a ribbon that protects your dream.
マイメロディー ハート見つけたなら
My Melody, if you find a heart...
グルグル巻きにしちゃうからね
I'll wrap it up round and round!
wow wow wo 覚悟しといて
Wow wow wo, be prepared!
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie.
オトナじゃない オトメです
I'm not an adult, I'm a young maiden.
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I might even end up crying.
女の子って魔法で 作られたの
Girls were made out of magic!
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Love love suu, fluffy fluffy fuu,
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
Feelings like this are a spellbound melody.
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody!
キライじゃない ってゆーかスキ
It's not that I hate it, more like I love it!
スナオになんてなれません
I just can't be honest about it.
君の笑顔見るだけで フニャフニャするの
Just seeing your smile makes me turn to mush.
それなのにー そっれなのに！
And yet... even so!
憎まれ口 撃ちまくり
Shooting off spiteful remarks,
ひとりになって 落ち込んで
Getting lonely and feeling down,
枕パンチ！！
Pillow punch!!
だから マイメロディー マイメロディー
So My Melody, My Melody!
本当の気持ち 風になって 結ぶリボン
My true feelings become the wind, tying a ribbon.
マイメロディー 歌えオトメゴコロ
My Melody, sing out a maiden's heart!
くるくる恋 つかまえちゃえ
Catch the spinning love!
WOW WOW WO 逃がさないから
WOW WOW WO 'cause I won't let you escape!
ここへ来て
Come over here!
キライじゃない ツライです(T_T)
It's not that I hate you, it's just painful (T_T)
真っ赤にだってなっちゃいます
I even turn bright red!
女の子って不思議で作られたの
Girls are made of mystery.
とどけ
Reach out,
マイメロディ マイメロディ
My Melody, My Melody!
星空を越えて
Crossing the starry sky,
君の夢 守るリボン
a ribbon that protects your dreams.
マイメロディ ハート見つけたら
My Melody, when I find your heart,
グルグル巻きにしちゃうからね
I'm going to wrap it round and round!
WOW WOW WO 覚悟しといて
WOW WOW WO, be prepared!
嘘じゃない
I'm not lying!
オトナじゃない オトメです
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden!
泣いたりで行っちゃいます
I even end up crying sometimes!
女の子って魔法で作られたの
Girls are made of magic!
スキスキスーフワフワフー
Love love love, fluffy fluffy fu~
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling is a melo-melody!
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody!
マイメロディ
My Melody!
なー！
Naa~!
ということで
And so...
最上級に可愛いのと
"Saijoukyuu ni Kawaii no" and
一途なシンデレラ
"Ichizu na Cinderella",
あと オトメロディー
plus "Otome Melody",
3曲連続で歌いましたー！
I sang three songs in a row~!
にゃー！
Nya~!
雲が晴れたステージってこうなってるのねー！
So this is what the stage looks like with the clouds cleared~!
すごーい！
Amazing~!
でっかい！舞踏会みたいなのねー！
It's huge! It's like a ball~!
あ、ここ見て！シャンデリアがあるのねー！
Ah, look here! There's a chandelier~!
ザ・舞踏会！ダンスするって感じなのねー！
It feels just like a real ball where everyone dances~!
あと、お城の上の方ってこうなってたんだー！
Also, so this is what the upper part of the castle looks like~!
見てー！
Look~!
すごい可愛いー！
It's super cute~!
ほらこれ、天窓じゃん！
Look, it's a skylight!
豪華なのねー！
It's so luxurious~!
すごい！あ、待って！Luna ReBirthDayの看板もあるのねー！
Wow! Ah, wait! There's a "Luna ReBirthDay" sign too~!
今日はLuna ReBirthDayだからね！
Because today is Luna ReBirthDay, you know!
見て見て！すごい可愛いー！
Look, look! It's super cute~!
ん？
Hm?
なんだなんだなんだ？
What is it, what is it?
最高だったよー！
That was amazing~!
え？ルーナイトやないかい！
Eh? Isn't that LuKnight?!
実はね、姫にはまだ隠された姿が残されているのて...
Actually, the Princess still has a hidden form remaining...
え？なななー？
Eh? Na-na-na~?
ルーナイトの魔法で、そのお姿にしてみせましょう！
With LuKnight magic, let us reveal that form to you!
え？何？
Eh? What?
ちちなの？
Chi-chi-na~?
じゃーん！
Ta-da~!
わー！すごい可愛いー！
Wow~! It's super cute~!
新しいヘアスタイルなのねー！
It's a new hairstyle~!
ルーナイトがプレゼントしてくれたのねー！
The LuKnights gave it to me as a present~!
よし！じゃあ、この新しい髪型で歌っちゃうのねー！
Alright! Then I'll sing with this new hairstyle~!
ア・ナ・タのアイドル
Your idol,
サインはB
Sign is B!
ようやく会えたね 嬉しいね
We finally met, I'm so happy!
持ち遠しくて 足をバッタバタしながら
I was looking forward to it so much, kicking my feet,
今日楽しみで 寝れなかったよ
I couldn't sleep because I was so excited for today!
（オレもー！）
(Me too!)
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない
This is no time to be nervous!
1分1秒 無駄になんてできないさ
Not a single minute or second can be wasted!
さあ 始めましょう
Now, let's begin!
君も！君も！君も！
You too! You too! You too!
お・ま・ち・ど・う・さ・ま
Thank you for waiting!
手を鳴らせ いらっしゃいませ
Clap your hands, welcome!
「好き」が集まる場所へようこそ
Welcome to the place where "likes" gather!
日常はクロークの中
Leave your everyday life in the cloakroom,
ここに来たなら 踊らにゃ 損 損
once you're here, you gotta dance or you're missing out!
客席が 居ようが 居まいが 関係ない
It doesn't matter if there's an audience or not!
会場が 大きい 小さい とか 気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small!
ちゃんと 見えてる
I can see them clearly,
君の サイリウム
your glowsticks!
今は フーっと吹けば 飛ぶような
Right now, it's like a tiny talent
小さな 小さな 才能だけど
that would blow away if you blew on it gently, but...
私を 推してくれるのなら
If you're going to support me...
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you maximum fanservice!
アナタのアイドル サインはB チュッ
Your idol, the sign is B! *Kiss*
あいつは俺が育てたって
"I raised that girl myself,"
近い将来 自慢してほしいよ
I want you to brag about it in the near future!
こうしちゃいられない
We can't just stand around!
君と！君と！今を！
With you! With you! The present!
楽しまなきゃ
We have to enjoy it!
引きこもりも人見知りも 普段と違う顔見せてよ
Shut-ins and wallflowers too, show me a side of you I don't usually see!
みんな兄弟 調子どうだい
How's everyone doing, brothers?
なりふり構わずに そう！そう！そう！
Without caring about appearances, yeah! yeah! yeah!
他人に笑われていても関係ない
It doesn't matter if people laugh at you!
周りがどうとかこうとか気にしない
Don't worry about what everyone else says!
主張強すぎ 君のサイリウム
Your glowstick stands out so much!
たとえ世界が私を拒んで ひとりぼっちを感じたとしても
Even if the world rejects me and I feel all alone,
アナタが味方でいてくれたら 怖いものはないよ
As long as you're on my side, there's nothing to be afraid of!
見てよ 見てよ 何かが始まる 君との物語が
Look, look, something is starting! Our story together!
嗚呼 なんて素晴らしい景色だ！
Ah, what a wonderful sight!
客席が居ようが居まいが関係ない
It doesn't matter if there's an audience or not,
会場が大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small!
ちゃんと見えてる 君のサイリウム
I can clearly see your glowstick!
今はフーっと吹けば飛ぶような
Right now, it's something that could blow away with a puff,
小さな小さな才能だけど
A tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を押してくれるのなら
If you're going to support me,
アナタが味方でいてくれたら
If you stay on my side,
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you maximum fanservice!
アナタのアイドル サインはB チュッ
Your idol, the sign is B! *Kiss*
絶対結婚しようなー！
Let's definitely get married!
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない 消してあげーる
I won't let romance scandals escape; I'll wipe them out for you.
宣誓！私が大統領になったら 人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします
Oath! When I become president, women who mess with taken men will be exiled to an island!
宣誓！私が大統領になったら いやただの友達だよ～って誤魔化す奴はヘソから電気を流します
Oath! When I become president, anyone who tries to play it off with "No, we're just friends~" will be shocked through their belly button!
だ・だ・だ・大胆不敵 センセーショナルクローズアップ
D-D-D-Daring and fearless, sensational close-up!
D, D, D, Don't cry やるぜ徹底的にリサーチだ
D-D-D-Don't cry, I'll do a thorough investigation!
大嫌い？しょうがない？ クズは病気ね バイバイ・バイ
Hate it? Can't be helped? Scum is a disease, bye-bye-bye!
権力！財産！地位名声！！ なんにもないけど裁きたいでしょ？
Power! Wealth! Status, fame!! You have none of those, but you still want to pass judgment, right?
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね まずは君を捕まえるね
When I-I-I become president, I'll catch you first!
濡れたタオルで 洗いざらい吐かせるね
With a wet towel, I'll make you confess everything!
誰ですかあの女 駄目ですかそうですか
Who is that woman? Is that wrong? Oh, I see.
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない 消してあげーる シル・ヴ・プレプレ プレジデント
I won't let romance scandals escape; I'll wipe them out! S'il vous ple-ple-president!
宣誓！私が大統領になったら ただの仕事の付き合いだよ？っていう奴は二度と働けなくしてやりまーす
Oath! When I become president, anyone who says "It's just a business relationship" will never work again!
宣誓！以下略！ いや向こうが強引でさ～っていう男の口にはレジンを流し込んで固めてやりまーす！
Oath! Abbreviating the rest! Any guy who says "She was too pushy~" will have resin poured into his mouth to harden!
み・み・み・密着 まるでドン・ファン気取りスキャンダラス
Cl-cl-cl-close contact! Playing Don Juan, how scandalous!
ま・ま・ま・末端価格 甲斐性なしのスクープね
St-st-st-street value! A useless scoop, isn't it?
愛はない？理由じゃない？ 悪くないのにはいはいはい
No love? Not a valid excuse? "I did nothing wrong," yeah, yeah, yeah!
軽薄！のうのう！いけしゃあしゃあ！！ なんにもないとかありえないでしょ？
Frivolous! Carefree! Shameless!! Saying "nothing happened" is completely impossible, right?
だ・だ・だ・大統領になってもね たぶん君は変わらないね
Even if I become-come-come president, you probably won't change, right?
しれっととぼけて のらりくらりかわすのね
You'll just play dumb and dodge the subject nonchalantly!
デートですかこんばんは 本気ですかそうですか
On a date tonight? Good evening. Are you serious? Oh, I see.
情熱とは不注意 微熱も消してしまいたい
Passion is carelessness; I want to extinguish even the slightest fever!
だ・だ・だ・大統領になったらね
If I become the President...
マジで君を捕まえるね
I'll seriously catch you!
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel,
洗いざらい吐かせるね
I'll make you confess everything!
どこですか 今あんた
Where are you right now?
見っけちゃった バレちゃった
Found you! You're busted!
夜道にはご用心 さよなら
Be careful on the dark streets at night, goodbye!
代わりに銃声
And gunshot sounds instead...
シル・ヴ・プレプレプレジデント
S'il vous Pre-Pre-President!
電波散布中 感電中
Radio waves broadcasting, electric shock in progress...
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
[Title: Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous]
あなたが抱え込んだ忘れたいこと 悲しいこと あるのか知らんね
Things you carry that you want to forget, sad things, who knows if you have them...
知らん映画なのに涙を流すのは ドラマチックが足りてないからよ
Crying at a movie you don't even know is because your life lacks drama!
そんな筋にも付かないこと くだらないこと 考えてばかりね
Always thinking about nonsensical, pointless things, aren't you?
目が合えば愛もしそらゆく顔も 誰かのものになるんでしょう
When eyes meet, love and averted faces will just belong to someone else, right?
そっぽ向くファンデーションも全部 誰かのため塗る
Even all this foundation turned away is applied for someone else's sake.
一体全体どうしてどうしてなぜなぜハテナ
Why on earth, why, why, question mark?
あてなんかねえな どこまでゆくの あなた一切合切放り出しても
No aim in sight, how far will you go? Even if you toss everything away...
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
You've got to be kidding, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たってどうにもならないぜ
When that moment comes, there's nothing you can do.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリーするだけ
Vague truth will only make you melancholy.
あたしはさ 重ねて今手噛み YES
And as for me, I bite my hand once again, YES!
完全におかしなハートばかり
Nothing but completely warped hearts,
誰も彼もビクともしないわ
not a single soul is shaken.
実体のない感情報道だって 策略の最優先なのになぜ
Even reporting baseless emotions is the top strategic priority, so why?
あぁもうこれ懲り懲りよ 私の勝手な気質もじっとこらえて 取り繕う手はとうとう限界点
Ah, I've had enough of this! Suppressing my selfish nature, my composure is at its limit!
年がら年中リップサービス
All year round, it's just lip service.
どっかんどっかん増してはへきへき どんガラガッシャンフィールガールは涙の目にも見
Surging up and growing fed up, the crashing feel-girl is blinded by tears.
今やあ たまのハノミューシックのせいで あなたの話は一向に聞き取れない
Now, thanks to the music playing occasionally, I can't catch a word of what you're saying.
少しはまともなこと言って イエイ
Say something that actually makes sense, yeah!
回り出したテーブルで全部 忘れさせてよ
Let me forget everything at this spinning table!
だけど一体全体どうしてどうしてなぜなぜハテナ
But why on earth, why, why, question mark?
あてなんかねえな 消えないままに あなた幾重にもすれ違っても
No aim in sight, remaining unextinguished, even if we pass each other repeatedly...
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
You've got to be kidding, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たってどうにもならないぜ
When that moment comes, there's nothing you can do.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリーするだけ
Vague truth will only make you melancholy.
あたしは今...
And I am now...
冗談じゃないわ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
You've got to be kidding, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たってどうにもならないぜ
When that moment comes, there's nothing you can do.
甲斐ないわ 感情なんて何取りで落とすだけ
It's pointless, dropping emotions with just a touch.
私と確かめ合っていよう街
In this city where we confirm things together,
アイアイヤ トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Ai-ai-ya Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous!
その時が来たってどうにもならないぜ
When that moment comes, there's nothing you can do.
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリーするだけ
Vague truth will only make you melancholy.
あたしはさ 重ねて今手噛み YES
And as for me, I bite my hand once again, YES!
二酸化炭素をはきだして
Exhaling carbon dioxide,
あの子が呼吸をしているよ
that child is breathing.
曇天模様の空の下
Under the overcast sky,
つぼみのままでゆれながら
swaying while still in bud.
野良犬はぼくの骨くわえ
A stray dog carries my bone in its mouth,
野性の力をためしてる
testing its wild instinct.
路地裏に月がおっこちて
The moon fell into a back alley,
犬の目玉は四角だよ
and the dog's eyeballs are square.
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time,
木星についたよ
humankind reached Jupiter.
ピテカントロプスになる日が
The day we turn into Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
has drawn near.
アラビアの笛の音響く
The sound of Arabian flutes echoes
街のはずれの夢のあと
After the dream at the edge of the town
つばさをなくしたペガサスが
A Pegasus that lost its wings
夜空にはしごをかけている
Is setting up a ladder in the night sky
武器をかついだ兵隊さん
Soldiers carrying weapons
南にいこうとしてるけど
Trying to head south
サーベルの音はチャラチャラと
The sound of sabers goes clattering away
街の空気を汚してる
Polluting the air of the town
今日 人類がはじめて 木星についたよ
Today, humankind reached Jupiter for the first time
ピテカントロプスになる日も 近づいたんだよ
The day we become Pithecanthropus is drawing near
歌を忘れたカナリア
The canary that forgot how to sing
牛を忘れた牛小屋
The cowshed that forgot its cows
こわれた磁石を ひろい集める博士は まるはげさ
The doctor gathering up broken magnets is completely bald
あの子は花火を打ち上げて
That child sets off fireworks
この日が来たのを祝ってる
Celebrating that this day has arrived
冬の花火は強すぎて
Winter fireworks are too strong
ぼくらの体はくだけ散る
Our bodies shatter to pieces
ブーゲンビリアの木の下で
Under the bougainvillea tree
ぼくはあの子を探すけど
I search for that child
月の光に邪魔されて
Interrupted by the moonlight
あの子のカケラは見つからない
I cannot find the pieces of that child
今日 人類がはじめて 木星についたよ
Today, humankind reached Jupiter for the first time
ピテカントロプスになる日も 近づいたんだよ
The day we become Pithecanthropus is drawing near
今日 人類がはじめて 木星についたよ
Today, humankind reached Jupiter for the first time
ピテカントロプスになる日も 近づいたんだよ
The day we become Pithecanthropus is drawing near
さるにはなりたくない
I don't want to become a monkey
こわれた磁石を 砂浜でひろっているだけさ
Just picking up broken magnets on the sandy beach
今日 人類がはじめて 木星についたよ
Today, humankind reached Jupiter for the first time
ピテカントロプスになる日も 近づいたんだよ
The day we become Pithecanthropus is drawing near
さるになるよ
I'll become a monkey
サンドリヨン
Cendrillon
朝まで踊る
Dancing until morning
夢だけ見せて
Show me only dreams
時計の鐘が
The clock's bell
解く魔法
Unlocks the magic
曖昧な指
Ambiguous fingers
誘う階段
Beckon down the stairs
三段飛ばしに跳ねていく
Skipping three steps at a time
馬車の中で
Inside the carriage
震えてた
Trembling
みじめな古着
Wretched old clothes
めくり廻れ
Swirling around
夜の舞踏
The night ball
見知らぬ顔探す
Searching for an unfamiliar face
囁くあの声が
That whispering voice...
握り締めた刃
The tightly gripped blade...
衝動突き立て すべてを奪えと
Driven by impulse, to take everything away.
孤児集う城
In the castle where orphans gather,
笑み仮面に描いて
painting a smile on a mask,
偽りの慈しみさえ
even false affection...
羽で包む
wrapped in wings...
熾天使
A seraphim.
灰の中で
In the ashes,
赤く溶けて
melting red...
混じる 硝子の靴
mixing together, glass slippers.
今更帰る 震えているの
It's too late to turn back now, am I trembling?
あなたが目をやる時計
The clock you glance at...
靴脱ぎ踊る スロープ抜けで
Taking off shoes to dance, slipping past the slope,
喉まで伸びる指の先で
with fingertips reaching to the throat...
すくう雫 口付けて
Scooping up droplets to kiss,
走る衝動 背骨抜けていく
a rushing impulse runs through the spine...
刹那
In an instant.
鐘は鳴らさないで
Don't let the bells ring,
あなたにひざまづき
kneeling before you,
まだダメと叫んだ
screaming "not yet",
右手が 突き刺すサヨナラ
my right hand stabs a farewell.
消せない硝煙を
Inerasable gunsmoke,
香水にまとう姫
a princess clad in perfume.
強い瞳 僕の凍った
Strong eyes, shooting through...
仮面ごと 撃ち抜く
...my frozen mask.
今も耳に あなたの吐息が
Even now in my ears, your breath...
突き刺さるの 遠い夢
...pierces through, a distant dream.
ステンドグラスごし 光る月が
The moon shining through the stained glass,
君にかぶせたベール
a veil cast over you.
ドレス 膝で裂いて
Tearing the dress at the knees,
ティアラは投げ捨てて
throwing away the tiara.
見つめあう瞳と瞳が
Gazing eyes meeting...
火花を放つ
...sparking flames.
孤独な魂が 炎あげ惹かれあう
Lonely souls ignite and attract each other.
その涙 すくえないなら まるで一人遊び
If I cannot save those tears, it's like playing alone.
時よ止まれ 今はあなたに酔いしれて
Time, stop now, let me get drunk on you.
揺れる鼓動 一つ一つを 刻み付けてたい
I want to engrave each and every trembling heartbeat.
とどまれ熱く濡れ
Stay, drenched in heat,
打ち付ける高まりに
in this pounding surge.
これ以上は動けないよ
I can't move any further...
まるで御伽噺
...just like a fairy tale.
みんな！ここからは大事なお知らせタイムなのら！
Everyone! From here on, it's time for important announcements nanora!
イエイ イエイ イエイ！
Yay, yay, yay!
ポルポル そこで見ててなのらね！
Pol-Pol, watch from over there, okay?
イエイ イエイ イエイ！
Yay, yay, yay!
では まずはこちら！
Now then! First, this one!
デデン！姫森ルーナ生誕記念2025のグッズが出まーす！
Ta-da! Himemori Luna Birthday Celebration 2025 merchandise is out!
イエイ！ではね こちら詳細見ていきましょう！
Yay! Now, let me show you the details!
デデン！ふたりのルーナ アクリルジオラマスタンドなのら！
Ta-da! Two Lunas Acrylic Diorama Stand nanora!
イラストはゾイロン先生に描いていただきました！
The illustration was drawn by Zoilon-sensei!
前のね 髪型と 今回のルーナのね 新しい髪型のルーナが
Luna with her previous hairstyle, and Luna with her new hairstyle...
そして 今回の生誕ライブのステージに登場しました！
...along with the stage from this birthday live, have all come together!
こちらはね 立体的なパーツが華やかで かわいい 素敵な 豪華仕様のジオラマスタンドになりました！
This became a gorgeous, cute, and wonderful diorama stand with glamorous 3D parts!
そして 次はこちら！
And next is this!
デデン！姫森ルーナぬいぐるみ 守ってルーナイトver.！
Ta-da! Himemori Luna Plushie: Protect Me LuKnight ver.!
なぁ
Hey,
守ってルーナイト ver.の
In the Protect LuNight ver. outfit,
姫ちゃんがぬいぐるみになりましたー！
Hime-chan became a plushie!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ぜひぜひみんなお家にお迎えして
Please bring me home to your house,
姫ちゃんをね、守ってほしいのらよ
and protect Hime-chan, okay?
そして次は、こちら！
And next, we have this!
デデン！ルーナイト2Wayバッグー！
Ta-da! LuNight 2-Way Bag!
さっきのぬいぐるみもすっぽり入ってしまう
Even the plushie from earlier fits snugly inside,
ルーナイトをアピールできるバッグになっています！
making it a bag to show off your LuNight pride!
バッグはね、なんとリュックにもなって
This bag can actually turn into a backpack,
超便利ー！
so it's super convenient!
デザインに使用されているモチーフは
The motifs used in the design
ルーナイト由来のものに統一しているので
are all unified with LuNight themes,
バッグモードでも
so whether in bag mode
リュックモードでも
or backpack mode,
お好きな方で使ってください！
please use whichever style you prefer!
次はこちら！
Next up is this!
デデン！ルーナイトカードホルダー！
Ta-da! LuNight Card Holder!
ルーナイト型のカードホルダーです！
It's a LuNight-shaped card holder!
チェキ風カードや
You can fit Cheki-style cards
ホロカのカードも入れられちゃうので
and HoloKa cards inside,
ルーナイトのみんなは
so all you LuNights,
こっちもしっかり守ってくださいね～
make sure to guard this securely too, okay?
そして、次はこちら！
And next, we have this!
デデン！ASMRボイス！
Ta-da! ASMR Voice!
『舞踏会の帰り道』
[On the Way Home from the Ball]
今回はね、舞踏会をイメージした
Since this year's birthday live
生誕祭ライブなので
was themed around a ball,
ルーナイトと二人きりになった
I made a voice pack of a moment
ひとときをボイスにしましたー！
spent alone with a LuNight!
馬車の中という
Inside a horse-drawn carriage,
密室で
in an enclosed space,
なんか急接近とかあっちゃうかもー！？
something like getting super close might happen...?!
ということで！
And so!
最後に改めてフルセットを見てみましょうー！
Lastly, let's look at the full set again!
こちら、フルセット購入特典はー
Here, the bonus for buying the full set is...
デデン！オリジナルカードー！
Ta-da! Original card!
イラストはソイルン先生で
The illustration is by Zoiln-sensei,
表面がチェキ風のカードになっています
and the front side is a Cheki-style card.
裏面は招待状風の
The back side is designed like an invitation,
デザインになっていてオシャレのら～！
which makes it super stylish!
そして！
And!
通常バージョンのフルセット購入特典は
the bonus for the standard full set
箔押し複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードー！
is a Cheki-style bromide card with a foil-stamped sign!
そしてー！
And...
数量限定バージョンのフルセット購入特典は
the bonus for the limited-quantity full set
直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードのらー！
is a Cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten signature!
みんな、ゲットしてほしいのら～！
Everyone, I hope you get it!
グッズはね、配信終了後
The merch will be available
販売開始でーす！
right after the stream ends!
そして、そして！
And, and!
もう一つ大事なお知らせがあります！
There's one more important announcement!
こちらー！
This!
『んなっしょいぱっしょん』
[Nnashoi Passion]
こちらをね、この後歌わせていただきます！
I'll be singing this song next!
みんなね
Everyone,
大好きな「んなっしょい」っていう言葉を使っているのでね
since I'm using my favorite word "Nnashoi",
みんなこの後いっぱい「んなっしょい」してのー！
make sure to spam "Nnashoi" a lot after this, okay?!
この配信がね、終わったら
Once this stream ends,
MVも公開されます！
the MV will also be released!
そして、MV公開後も
And even after the MV release,
念願が、今回初めてやることになったので
something I've always wished for will happen for the first time,
こちらもお楽しみにー！
so please look forward to that too!
ではね、歌いまーす！
Now then, I'm going to sing!
『んなっしょいぱっしょん』！
[Nnashoi Passion]!
な な な 泣きたい
Na, na, na, I wanna cry
別に大きくかねぇのら！
It's not like I'm big or anything!
むにゃい むにゃい 目をこする
Rubbing my sleepy eyes,
囚われた城に
in this captive castle,
パーフェクトな朝
a perfect morning.
おない おない お布団
No, no blanket,
飛び出して海へ行こう
let's jump out and head to the sea!
神様だって 間違ウンだって
They say even gods make mistakes,
よくある話だ そうです
that's a common story, it seems.
姫様にね 見とれちゃうだって
They say they get captivated by the princess,
やれやれ なのらね
oh dear, goodness me.
夢を夢見て 恋に恋して 生きていたい
Dreaming of dreams, falling in love, I want to live.
だから これでいいのら！
So this is fine as it is!
な な な 泣きたい
Na, na, na, I wanna cry,
ハラハラ笑いたい
I wanna laugh out loud,
心だってうりゃって変えるのら！
I'll even change my heart with a roar!
だから会いたい
So I want to meet you,
その願いに
to that wish,
いま約束の合言葉
now, our promised password!
行くよ んなっしょい！！
Here we go, Nnashoi!!
まどろみも ホラーな夜もあるけど
There are drowsy times and scary nights, but
でもね んなっしょい！！
even so, Nnashoi!!
いつまでもみんな
Forever, everyone,
お湯から平気
straight out of the warm bath,
まだ遊び足りねぇのら！
I still haven't played enough!
暗い 暗い 夜の中
Inside the dark, dark night,
ティアラをお外して
taking off my tiara,
城を抜け出たら
once I slip out of the castle,
深い 深い 海に出て
heading out into the deep, deep sea,
…バレてんのラクとないとー
...it's total bliss when nobody notices!
姫様はね
You know, the Princess...
わがままなんて おとぎのお話よ そうでしょう？
being selfish is just a fairy tale, right?
何がなんだって わたしなんだって
No matter what, because it's me,
これでいいのら！
this is just fine, nora!
んな んな んな なりたい わたしでいたい！
Nna nna nna, I want to become, I want to stay as myself!
どこへだって向かっていけるのら！
I can head anywhere I want, nora!
ならばしょうがない この想いに 今許される合言葉
Well then, it can't be helped—for these feelings, the secret phrase permitted right now!
いくよっ んなっしょい！
Here we go, Nnashoi!
サンゴ礁 白い砂浜も綺麗 そこに
Coral reefs, white sandy beaches are pretty too, over there...
んなっしょい！！ 輝くわたし
Nnashoi!! A shining me!
Q. 帰る理由は？ A. そこになければねぇのら！
Q. Reason to return home? A. If it's not there, there is none, nora!
んなあああああい！
Nnaaaaaai!
りぴーと あふた みー
Repeat after me!
んなっしょい！ んなっしょい！
Nnashoi! Nnashoi!
せーのっ
Ready, set, go!
んなっしょい！ んなっしょい！
Nnashoi! Nnashoi!
もう1回！
One more time!
んなっしょい！ んなっしょい！
Nnashoi! Nnashoi!
いいねぇ 熱い視線が集中
Nice! Passionate eyes are locked on us,
ハラハラする心に無我夢中 だから
completely absorbed in a thrilling heart, so...
だから
That's why...
これでいいのら！
this is just fine, nora!
んな んな んな 泣きたい から笑いたい
Nna nna nna, wanting to cry, so wanting to laugh!
心だって奪ってあげるのら！
I'll even steal your heart for you, nora!
だから「会いたい」 その願いに 今約束の合言葉
So for that wish of "I want to see you", the promised secret phrase right now!
いくよっ んなっしょい！
Here we go, Nnashoi!
まどろみも ホラーな夜もあるけど でもね
There are sleepy dozes and scary horror nights, but still...
んなっしょい！！ この先もみんな おりゆからへーき
Nnashoi!! Everyone will be around from now on too, so it's all good!
まだ遊び足りねぇのら！
I haven't played enough yet, nora!